This is how I win.
Uncut Gems is a drama, thriller, crime film directed by Benny Safdie.
A charismatic New York City jeweler always on the lookout for the next big score makes a
series of high-stakes bets that could lead to the windfall of a lifetime.
Howard must perform a precarious high-wire act, balancing business, family, and
encroaching adversaries on all sides in his relentless pursuit of the ultimate win.
Howard Ratner, played by Adam Sandler.
Demany, played by LaKeith Stanfield.
Julia De Flore, played by Julia Fox.
Kevin Garnett, played by Kevin Garnett.
Dinah Ratner, played by Idina Menzel.
Arno Moradian, played by Eric Bogosian.
Uncut Gems  is a 2019 American crime thriller film directed by Josh and
Benny Safdie, who wrote the screenplay with Ronald Bronstein.
The film stars Adam Sandler, LaKeith Stanfield, Julia Fox,
Kevin Garnett, Idina Menzel, and Eric Bogosian.
The film tells the story of Howard Ratner, a Jewish-American jeweler and gambling addict who
must retrieve an expensive gem he purchased in order to pay off his debt.
Filming took place from September to November 2018.
The original score is by Daniel Lopatin.
The film premiered at the 46th Telluride Film Festival on August 30, 2019.
A24 gave it a limited release in the United States on
December 13 and a wide release on December 25.
Uncut Gems was a box-office success and received acclaim, especially for Sandler's
against-type performance, which several reviewers called the best of his career.
The film was chosen by the National Board of Review
as one of the top ten films of 2019.
The film explores themes of bet, infidelity, new york city, gambling, auction.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.